(Sheldon:)Is it true, as a child,
you were a stutterer
(Sheldon:)and were functionally
mute for eight years?
(James:)It is true.
(Sheldon:)Is it true they used scuba gear
(Sheldon:)to create the sound of
Darth Vader breathing?
(James:)-They sure did.
-Oh.
(Sheldon:)Is it true that you
were pre-med in college
(Sheldon:)and you almost became a doctor?
(James:)-That's right.
-Oh, James!
(Sheldon:)I could listen
to your stories all night.
(Penny:)I mean, really, what's
so great about being grown up?
(Bernadette:)Well, for starters, we'd be
splitting this check three ways.
(Penny:)I'm serious.
Who wants to do all that stuff?
(Penny:)Have insurance, pay mortgages,
(Penny:)leave one of those little notes
when you hit a parked car.
(Amy:)I told you it was Penny.